Guide to the Henry Adams La Farge Papers Relating to a Catalogue Raisonné of Works by John La Farge
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Provenance Correspondence, Series III; 9.18; (23 boxes)
  - Paintings, Drawings, Engravings, Miscellaneous Decoration, Watercolors
    - Howell, Mary (Box 27)
    - Howe, Bruce (Box 27)
    - Howell (Box 27)
    - The Hudson River Museum (Box 27)
    - Hughes, Judith (Box 27)
    - Hummel, Sam (Box 27)
    - Hunnewell, Arnold W. (Box 27)
    - Hunt, Richard Morris (Box 27)
    - Hunter Museum of Art (Box 27)
    - Huntington, Chris (Box 27)
    - Huntington Galleries (Box 27)
    - The Huntington Library (Box 27)
    - Iacomo, Francis (Box 27)
    - IBM Gallery of Science and Art (Box 27)
    - Indiana University Art Museum (Box 27)
    - Indianapolis Museum of Art (Box 27)
    - Jaccaci family (Box 27)
    - Jackson family (Box 27)
    - James, William, III (Box 27)
    - Jenove, Edward H. (Box 27)
    - Johnson, Phyllis La Farge (Box 27)
    - Johnstone (Box 27)
    - Jones, Benjamin F. (Box 27)
    - Jones, Mary Cadwalader (Box 27)
    - The Jordan-Vople Gallery (Box 27)
    - Judd, Peter H. (Box 27)
    - Kaledin, Eugenia (Box 27)
    - Kaufmann, Jane D. (Box 27)
    - Kelly, June (Box 27)
    - Kemper, Crosby R. (Box 27)
    - Kennedy Galleries, 2 (Box 27)
    - King, Robert B. (Box 27)
    - Kline, Fred (Box 27)
    - Knapp, Faith (Box 27)
    - Knight-Gruberman, Joyce (Box 27)
    - Knobloch, Hilda (Box 28)
    - Knoedler-Modarco, S. A. (Box 28)
    - Knox, Mary (Box 28)
    - Kohler, Walter J., III (Box 28)
    - Korbel, Jane (Box 28)
    - Kowalski (Box 28)
    - Kraushaar Galleries (Box 28)
    - Kumm, Marguerite (Box 28)
    - Labate, Michael D., II (Box 28)
    - Laing, Mary E. D. (Box 28)
    - Lalli, Charles B. (Box 28)
    - Lane, Francis B. (Box 28)
    - Laurent, John (Box 28)
    - Lee family (Box 28)
    - Lefor, Patricia J. (Box 28)
    - Thurber, Arthur and Diana (Box 28)
    - Leninski (Box 28)
    - Leuchs, Fredrick and Marie (Box 28)
    - Lidgerwood, Harriet B. (Box 28)
    - Light, Robert M. (Box 28)
    - Lincoln, Mrs. R. C. (Box 28)
    - Little, Warren M. (Box 28)
    - Lobdell, Francis (Box 28)
    - Lowei-Robertson, INC. (Box 28)
    - Lombardo, Jovin C. (Box 28)
    - Long family (Box 28)
    - Longyear, John Munro (Box 28)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art (Box 28)
    - Lothrop family (and Abbott) (Box 28)
    - Louvre (Box 28)
    - Love, Harry (Box 28)
    - Love, Richard H. (Box 28)
    - Lovette, Stephen M. (Box 28)
    - Low, Will (Box 28)
    - Lowell family (Box 28)
    - The Lowe Art Museum (Box 28)
    - Lowe, David Garrand (Box 28)
    - Lunde, Eleanor S. (Box 28)
    - Lundstrum, Robin M. (Box 28)
    - Lyman family (Box 28)
    - Lyman Allyn Museum (Box 28)
    - Lynes, Mildred (Box 28)
    - Lyon, Cecil B. (Box 28)
    - Mac Beth Gallery Inc. (Box 28)
    - Maddox, Kenneth W. (Box 28)
    - Magriel (Box 28)
    - Maher, Jim (Box 28)
    - Malloy, E. (Box 28)
    - Malone, Mrs. Fredrick (Box 28)
    - Mandel, Patricia C. F. (Box 28)
    - Mann, Alvin (Box 28)
    - Manoogian, Richard A. (Box 28)
    - Marlor, Dr. Clark S. (Box 28)
    - Maroney, James H., Jr. (Box 28)
    - Marquand, Henry (Box 28)
    - Marsh, Michael (Box 28)
    - Mason family (and Sargent) (Box 28)
    - Mather, Frank Jewett, Jr. (Box 28)
    - Maxwell Galleries, Ltd. (Box 28)
    - McCabe, David A. (Box 28)
    - McCarron, Paul (Box 28)
    - McClintock, John and Mary (Box 28)
    - McDonough, John J., M.D. (Box 29)
    - McEwan, Thomas J. (Box 29)
    - McIntyre, Robert G. (Box 29)
    - McKean family (Box 29)
    - McLean H ospital (Box 29)
    - McNally, Sean M. (Box 29)
    - McNay Art Museum (Box 29)
    - Meixner, Laura (Box 29)
    - Mellar (Box 29)
    - Merriam, John D. (Box 29)
    - Merriman family (Box 29)
    - Metropolitan Club (Box 29)
    - The Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 29)
    - Miami University (Box 29)
    - Middendorf, Isabelle (Box 29)
    - Miller family (Box 29)
    - Milwaukee Art Center exhibit (Box 29)
    - Minneapolis murals (Box 29)
    - Mint Museum of Art (Box 29)
    - Mitchell, John (Box 29)
    - Molnar, Elizabeth (Box 29)
    - The Museum of Modern Art (Box 29)
    - Montgomery Gallery (Box 29)
    - Moore, Ann (Box 29)
    - Moreno, Leopold S., M.D. (Box 29)
    - Morgan Library (Box 29)
    - Morgan State University (Box 29)
    - Morrison, Mrs. James (Box 29)
    - Grubman, Caroline M. (Box 29)
    - Moshar, Donald Allen (Box 29)
    - Mount Saint Mary's College (Box 29)
    - Murphy, Mrs. William (Box 29)
    - Murray, Richard N. (Box 29)
    - National Academy of Design (Box 29)
    - Naeve, Milo M. (Box 29)
    - Nash, Arthur L. (Box 29)
    - Nassau County Museum of Art (Box 29)
    - National Gallery of Art (Box 29)
    - National Gallery of Scotland (Box 29)
    - National Museum of American Art- La Farge Exhibition 1987-1988 (Box 29)
    - The National Portrait Gallery (Box 29)
    - The Nelson-Atkins Museum of Art (Box 30)
    - The New Britain Museum of Modern Art (Box 30)
    - The Newark Museum (Box 30)
    - Newark Public Library (Box 30)
    - Newhouse, Jill (Box 30)
    - New Orleans Museum of Art (Box 30)
    - Newport Art Museum (Box 30)
    - Newport Congregational Church (Box 30)
    - Newton, George N. (Box 30)
    - New York City Appellate Court (Box 30)
    - The New York Cultural Center (Box 30)
    - New York Historical Society (Box 30)
    - Notman (Box 30)
    - Oberlin College (Box 30)
    - O'Gorman, James F. (Box 30)
    - O'Reilly (Box 30)
    - Osborn, Margaret La Farge (Box 30)
    - Ostberg, Henry D. (Box 30)
    - O'Toole, Patricia (Box 30)
    - Pacific Asia Museum (Box 30)
    - Paine family (Box 30)
    - Panicali Fine Art (Box 30)
    - Parker family (Box 30)
    - Parmelee, Terry and John (Box 30)
    - Parsons, Mrs. Frank W. (Box 30)
    - Partridge, William (Box 30)
    - Paulin, E. J. (Box 30)
    - Payson, Sandra (Box 30)
    - Peabody Museum (exhibition) (Box 30)
    - Penny, Samuel (Box 30)
    - Penta, Bob (Box 30)
    - Pentz, Herbert C. (Box 30)
    - Perry family (Box 30)
    - Philadelphia Museum of Art (Box 30)
    - Phillip, Mrs. M. Bernard (Box 30)
    - Phillips Auctioneers (Box 30)
    - The Phillips Collection (Box 30)
    - Pickhardt (Box 30)
    - Pindell, Pamela (Box 30)
    - Pivar, Stuart (Box 31)
    - Platt, Mrs. Haviland H. (Box 31)
    - Plowden, John (Box 31)
    - Polich, Yoni (Box 31)
    - Poore, Barbara S. (Box 31)
    - Porter, Ken (Box 31)
    - Porter, Milton (Box 31)
    - Portland, Maine, churches (Box 31)
    - Portsmouth Abbey School (Box 31)
    - Post Road Gallery (Box 31)
    - Potamkin, Mr. and Mrs. Meyer P. (Box 31)
    - Potter, Mrs. John B. (Box 31)
    - Potter family (Box 31)
    - The Preservation Society of Newport County (Box 31)
    - Previti family (Box 31)
    - Prince family (Box 31)
    - Princeton University (Box 31)
    - Prout, Daphne (Box 31)
    - Putnam (Box 31)
    - Arthur M. Sackler Gallery (Box 31)
    - Sadik, Marvin (Box 31)
    - Salm, Count Peter (Box 31)
    - Salmon, Tati (Box 31)
    - Sampson collection (Box 31)
    - Samuels, Harold and Peggy (Box 31)
    - Sanborn, Noel Byron (Box 31)
    - San Diego Museum of Art (Box 31)
    - San Francisco museums (Box 31)
    - Santa Barbara Museum of Art (Box 31)
    - Sargent, Mr., Sr. (Box 31)
    - Savorgnan, Mrs. (Box 31)
    - Scherer, Marty (Box 31)
    - Schirmer (Box 31)
    - Schlossman, Abraham (Box 31)
    - Schmidt family (Box 31)
    - Schoelkopt, Jane (Box 31)
    - Schwarzchild, Priscilla (Box 31)
    - Schweitzer Gallery (Box 31)
    - Scribner's Monthly (Box 31)
    - Scudder (Riverside Magazine) (Box 31)
    - Scripps College (Box 31)
    - Seeley, Barea Lamb (Box 31)
    - Seitz (Box 31)
    - Seligmen, Eustace (Box 31)
    - Sellin, David (Box 31)
    - Seymour, Cyrus (Box 31)
    - Shattuck, George H., Jr. (Box 31)
    - Shaw family (Box 31)
    - Shepard, Edward M., M.D. (Box 31)
    - Shepard Gallery (Box 31)
    - Sherman, Edward A. (Box 31)
    - Shoemaker, Mark E. (Box 31)
    - Skinner, Robert W. (Box 31)
    - Sloan (auctions) (Box 31)
    - Smith College Museum of Art (Box 31)
    - Smolev, Dr. and Mrs. Joseph (Box 31)
    - Sotheby's (Box 31)
    - Spanierman Gallery (Box 31)
    - Spark, Victor D. (Box 32)
    - Spencer, Ralph and Florence (Box 32)
    - S.P.N.A. (Box 32)
    - Sprague-Smith (Box 32)
    - Spring Creek Art Foundation (Box 32)
    - Springfield Museum of Fine Arts (Box 32)
    - Stapinski, Stephen E. (Box 32)
    - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus (Box 32)
    - Saint-Gaudens National Historic Site (Box 32)
    - The St. Louis Art Museum (Box 32)
    - St. Patrick's Cathedral (Box 32)
    - St. Paul the Apostle (Box 32)
    - St. Peter's Church- Hartford, Connecticut (Box 32)
    - St. Petersburg Museum of Fine Arts (Box 32)
    - St. Thomas Church (Box 32)
    - Stackpole, Kathryn Howland (Box 32)
    - Staten Island Institute of Arts and Sciences (Box 32)
    - Stebbins (Box 32)
    - Stickney (Box 32)
    - Stillman, Chauncey (Box 32)
    - Stokes family (Box 32)
    - Storer, Ethel (Box 32)
    - Storey family (Box 32)
    - Storrow family (Box 32)
    - Streeter, Mary Ann (Box 32)
    - Strouth, Mr. (Box 32)
    - Sturgis family (Box 32)
    - Strum, James L. (Box 32)
    - Swan (Box 32)
    - Swann (Box 32)
    - Swarthmore College (Box 32)
    - Symington family (Box 32)
    - Syracuse University (Box 32)
    - Szapary, Sylvia (Box 32)
    - Talbot, Stuart (Box 32)
    - Tanzer (Box 32)
    - Taylor (and Miller) (Box 32)
    - Terner, Jacob Y., M.D. (Box 32)
    - Terra, Daniel J. (Box 32)
    - Thomas, Joseph B. (Box 32)
    - Thoron (Box 32)
    - Tivoli Galleries (Box 32)
    - The Toledo Museum of Art (Box 32)
    - Toussaint, Pierre (Box 32)
    - Trafford (Box 32)
    - Transco Energy Company (Box 32)
    - Trask (Box 32)
    - Trinity Church in the City of Boston (Box 32)
    - Trinity Church- Buffalo, New York (Box 32)
    - Turner (Box 32)
    - Union League (Box 32)
    - University of California, Santa Barbara (Box 32)
    - University of Chicago (Box 32)
    - University of Georgia (Box 32)
    - University of Kansas (Box 32)
    - University of Michigan Museum of Art (Box 32)
    - University of Minnesota (Box 33)
    - University of Nebraska (Box 33)
    - University of New Mexico (Box 33)
    - University of Utah (Box 33)
    - Upjohn, Everard (Box 33)
    - Vanderbilt, Cornelius, mansion, 3 (Box 33)
    - Vanderbilt, William H. (Box 33)
    - Van Horne (Box 33)
    - Vareika, William (Box 33)
    - Vaughn (Box 34)
    - The Vault Art Trust (Box 34)
    - Vedder (Box 34)
    - Tom Veilleux Gallery (Box 34)
    - Vernon family (and Craig) (Box 34)
    - Villard-Helmsley (Box 34)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box 34)
    - Voorsanger, Catherine (Box 34)
    - Votive wreath painting labels [?] (Box 34)
    - Wadsworth Antheneum (Box 34)
    - Wahl (Walcott) (Box 34)
    - Wadsworth family (Box 34)
    - Walker family (Box 34)
    - Walker, Wendy (Box 34)
    - Walters Art Gallery (Box 34)
    - Ward, Brian R. (Box 34)
    - Ware, Charles Eliot (Box 34)
    - Warner family (Box 34)
    - Warren, Joseph, etc. (Box 34)
    - Warren, Lewis and family (Box 34)
    - Warre, Samuel D., etc. (Box 34)
    - Washington County Museum (Box 34)
    - Webster, Frank, etc. (Box 34)
    - Webster, Sally (Box 34)
    - Weimann, Robert Paul, III (Box 34)
    - Weinberg (Box 34)
    - Weitenkampf, Frank (Box 34)
    - Wellesley College (Box 34)
    - Wells, Arnold (Box 34)
    - Westmoreland County Museum of Art (Box 34)
    - Wetmore (Box 34)
    - Weyhe Gallery (Box 34)
    - Wheelwright (Box 34)
    - White family (Box 34)
    - Whitin (Box 34)
    - Whitney (Box 34)
    - Wichita Art Museum (Box 34)
    - Williams College (Box 34)
    - Williams, J. Lanier (Box 34)
    - Williamson family (Box 34)
    - Williford, Graham (Box 34)
    - Winner, Viola Hopkins (Box 34)
    - Winslow, John G. (Box 35)
    - Wood family (Box 35)
    - Wolf's Auctioneers and Appraisers (Box 35)
    - Woodward, Stanley (Box 35)
    - Worcester Art Museum (Box 35)
    - Wores, Theodore (Box 35)
    - Worman, Paul (Box 35)
    - Worthington (Box 35)
    - Wren, Linnea (Box 35)
    - Wulsin (Box 35)
    - Yale University, 2 (Box 35)
    - Yarnall, James L. (Box 35)
    - Yarnell, Sam I. (Box 35)
    - Young Art Gallery (Box 35)
    - Yulee House (Box 35)
    - Zakow, Joel (Box 35)
- Other Research and Correspondence Files, Series IV; 4.8; (12 boxes)
  - La Farge, Aimie (Box 36)
  - La Farge, Bancel (Box 36)
  - La Farge, Charles (Box 36)
  - La Farge, C. Grant (Box 36)
  - La Farge Decorative Arts Company (Box 36)
  - La Farge, John (Box 36)
    - Letters to parents (Box 36)
    - Java diary (Box 36)
    - Letters etc. from the Lamb Archives (Box 36)
    - Autograph orginals (Box 36)
    - Letters to Childs, Edward H. (Box 36)
    - Letters to Mather (Box 36)
    - Obituaries (Box 36)
    - Miscellany (includes articles and book excerpts) (Box 36)
    - Report to Bing (Box 36)
  - La Farge, Rev. John S. J. [?] (Box 36)
  - La Farge, John Frederick (Box 36)
  - La Farge, Henry (curriculum vitae, bibliography, Courtauld article), 2 (Box 36)
  - La Farge, L. Bancel (Box 36)
  - La Farge, Mrs. John (Box 37)
  - Various obituaries (Box 37)
  - La Farge, Mabel (Box 37)
  - La Farge, Oliver Hazard Perry (Box 37)
  - La Farge, Sheila (Box 37)
  - La Farge, Timothy (Box 37)
  - Obituaries/Genealogy (General) (Box 37)
  - Aborn, Milton (Box 37)
  - Adams, Andrew (Box 37)
  - Adams, William B. (Box 37)
  - Ames family (Box 37)
  - Amory, Mrs. Robert G. (Box 37)
  - Anderson family (Box 37)
  - Ayer, Mary Elisha Farwell (Box 37)
  - Baker, Richard and Alice (Box 37)
  - Bangs, Edward (Box 37)
  - Bancroft, John Chandler (Box 37)
  - Barton family (Box 37)
  - Beard, William H. (Box 37)
  - Blake, George Baty (Box 37)
  - Bliss, George T. (Box 37)
  - Bowen, Clarence Winthrop (Box 37)
  - Brice, Calvin S. (Box 37)
  - Brimmer, Martin (Box 37)
  - Brimmer, Mary Ann (Box 37)
  - Brooks family (Box 37)
  - Brouillette, Telles Gilbert (Box 37)
  - Brown, Martin Bartholomew (Box 37)
  - Buffalo, New York- Trinity Church (donors and honorees) (Box 37)
  - Bush, Samuel Dacre (Box 37)
  - Cabot, Susan Burley (Box 37)
  - Caldwell family (Box 37)
  - Coffin, Edmund (Box 37)
  - Coolidge, Algernon (Box 37)
  - Cortissoz, Royal (Box 37)
  - Cresmer, William T. (Box 37)
  - Cyler, Lewis B. (Box 37)
  - Dorsheimer, William (Box 37)
  - Drake, Alexander Wilson (Box 37)
  - Dwight, Frederick (Box 37)
  - Eads, James Buchanan (Box 37)
  - Elliot, John Morse (Box 37)
  - Emmerton, Caroline O. (Box 37)
  - Emmet family (Box 37)
  - Engel, Julia B. (Box 37)
  - Field, Cyrus (Box 37)
  - Fillin, Lucille (Box 37)
  - Otto, Fukushima (Box 37)
  - Gilbert, Bradford Lee (Box 37)
  - Hammond, Ellen S. S. (Box 37)
  - Haupt, Ira (Box 37)
  - Hecker family (Box 37)
  - Heinigke, Otto (Box 37)
  - Higginson family (Box 37)
  - Hill, James Norman and James J. (Box 37)
  - Holiday, Henry (Box 37)
  - Homans, George (Box 37)
  - Hotchkiss, Henry Lucius (Box 37)
  - Howes, Miss E. H. (Box 37)
  - Huebsch family (Box 37)
  - Humbert, Arthur Cleveland (Box 37)
  - Hunnewell family (Box 37)
  - Johnstone, J. J. Humphrey (Box 37)
  - Jones, Benjamin M. (Box 37)
  - Jones, Caroline M. (Box 37)
  - Kidder, Henry P. (Box 37)
  - Kinnicutt, Lincoln Newton (Box 37)
  - Kohler, Dorothy (Box 37)
  - Kunhardt, Henry Rudolph (Box 37)
  - La Farge, Bancel (Box 37)
  - Lamont, Daniel S. (Box 37)
  - Lathrop, Francis (Box 37)
  - Little, E. (Box 37)
  - Longyear, John M. (Box 37)
  - Longyear, Mary Beecher (Box 37)
  - Lowell, Amy (Box 37)
  - Lowell, Georgina (Box 37)
  - Lowell, John (Box 37)
  - Marquand, Henry Gordon (Box 37)
  - Mayer, John (Box 37)
  - McClure, Harriet Hurd (Box 37)
  - McFadden, Louis Ettlinger (Box 37)
  - Maguire, Frank J. (Box 37)
  - Morrisey, W. G., Jr. (Box 37)
  - Mygatt, Robertson K. (Box 37)
  - Nell, Munoz (Box 37)
  - Nimmo, J. (Box 37)
  - Parsons, Rev. Arthur T. (Box 37)
  - Parsons family of New Hampshire (Box 37)
  - Peckham, William G. (Box 38)
  - Pierson, Gen. Charles (Box 38)
  - Perry, Oliver Hazard (Box 38)
  - Plowden family of Seattle (Box 38)
  - Pratt, Frederic B. (Box 38)
  - Rehn, F. K. M (Box 38)
  - Rice, Edward (Box 38)
  - Sampson, Alden (Box 38)
  - Sampson, Prof. Edward (Box 38)
  - Sanborn, N. (Box 38)
  - Sayles, Henry F. (Box 38)
  - Sears, Knyvet Winthrop (Box 38)
  - Seligmann, Andre (Box 38)
  - Shaw, Francis (Box 38)
  - Shaw, G. Howland (Box 38)
  - Sherman, William Watts (Box 38)
  - Sprague-Smith, Mrs. Charles (Box 38)
  - Stetson, Mrs. (Box 38)
  - Stockton (Box 38)
  - Storrow, James J. (Box 38)
  - Tappan, Mary Ann (Box 38)
  - Thomas, Joseph B. (Box 38)
  - Thomas, Frank (& sons) (Box 38)
  - Trowbridge, Henry (Box 38)
  - Ticknor, Anna Eliot (Box 38)
  - Tuckerman, Emily (Box 38)
  - Van Choate family (Box 38)
  - Wadsworths of Geneseo (Box 38)
  - Warren family of Boston (Box 38)
  - Warren family of Buffalo (Box 38)
  - Wheelwright, Mrs. Edward (Box 38)
  - Woodward, Samuel B. (Box 38)
  - Wulsin, Mrs. Lucien (Box 38)
  - Yulee, David (Box 38)
  - La Farge, Margaret (Box 38)
  - Baltimore- Edmund Church (Box 38)
  - Pittsburgh- Frick building and Burnham of Chicago (Box 38)
  - Baltimore- Garrett-Jacobs house and Evergreen (Garrett) (Box 38)
  - Copyrights (Box 38)
  - Lawsuits vs. John La Farge (Box 38)
  - Columbia and Princeton letters (Box 38)
  - North Easton, Massachusetts (Box 39)
  - Exhibit information (Box 39)
  - Tenth Street Studio (Box 39)
  - Thomas Gaffield Papers, MIT Libraries (Box 39)
  - Reviews and descriptions of John La Farge's works (Box 39)
  - Middletown and Newport- United Congregational Church records (Box 39)
  - Patents- La Farge, Tiffany, and Tillinghast (Box 39)
  - The Stained Glass Windows in Memorial Hall, 2 (Box 39)
  - St. Gaudens correspondence with John La Farge- Dartmouth, 2 (Box 40)
  - Perry and La Farge, letters and diaries (Box 40)
  - John La Farge correspondence and other records at the Boston Museum of Fine Art (Box 40)
  - Various notes on John La Farge (Box 40)
  - Commentaries and notes for a slide lecture in Buffalo (Box 40)
  - Typescripts of letters by John La Farge (Box 40)
  - Development of the Stained Glass Industry in the United States, outline, Ruddock, Martin D. (Box 40)
  - Sources for descriptions, etc. (Box 40)
  - Correspondence with Adams, Henry (Box 41)
  - Catalogue project material (Box 41)
  - Munford, Howard M. (Box 42)
  - Rhoads, William B. (Box 42)
  - Rhys, Prof. Hedley H. (Box 42)
  - Riggio, Bob (Box 42)
  - Rhode Island School of Design (Box 42)
  - Richards, Miss (Box 42)
  - Robertson, Dr. (Box 42)
  - Robinson, Geoffrey H. (Box 42)
  - Rumsey, Charles and R. Douglas (Box 42)
  - Russell, Joseph, Jr. (Box 42)
  - Ryan, Joseph J. (Box 42)
  - Rand, Mrs. William (Box 42)
  - Raydon Gallery (Box 42)
  - Reading Museum and Library (Box 42)
  - Read, Helen Appleton and Jean B. (Box 42)
  - Reid, Horise (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous notes and correspondence, 4 (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous notes and correspondence, 4 (Box 43)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities grant (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous notes and correspondence, 2 (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous notes and correspondence, 5 (Box 44)
  - John La Farge exhibit catalogues 1866-1907, 2 (Box 44)
  - Later exhibit catalogues (Box 45)
  - Outline and sample chapters for a "Life of John La Farge" (Box 45)
  - Transcript of letters relating to letterpress books (Box 45)
  - John La Farge read by H. Mayor (Box 45)
  - Notebook (Box 45)
  - Drafts and notes, 2 (Box 45)
  - Notebooks, 3 (Box 45)
  - Notebooks, 4 (Box 46)
  - "John La Farge's Conversation" by Miss Viola Roseboro (Box 46)
  - Visual copy-caster (Box 46)
  - Photographs and prints of paintings, 3 (Box 46)
  - Duplicate photographs, 3 (Box 46)
  - Provenance information, 4 (Box 47)
  - Photocopies of La Farge's works, 2 (Box 47)